plrexperts.com 2018-11-26

# Privacy Policy Introduction

Privacy Policy
Introduction
Here in Wealthy PLR Limited (WealthyPLR.com, PLRExperts.com,
SuperAffiliateCenter.com), Owner: Jonathan Teng, myself and my team are
totally committed to keeping your personal data safe. We will always treat
your personal data with respect and deliver services to our clients with
privacy in mind.
This privacy policy will help you understand how we collect, use and protect
your personal data.
Who we are:
Wealthy PLR Limited
Data we collect
We collect personal data, and may collect special category personal data, as
part of providing legal services to our clients. We may also monitor or record
calls, emails, SMS messages or other communications in accordance with UK
law.
Types of data we may collect
How your data is used (Legal Services Clients)
How your data is used (Litigation Friends, Persons Acting Under a Power of
Attorney or as Court Appointed Deputies)
How your data is used (Witnesses of Fact)
How your data is used (Authorised Callers)
How your data is used (Individual Suppliers and Experts)
Wealthy PLR Limited Legitimate Interests
There are certain circumstances where we process your personal data for
our legitimate business interests. These can be, for example, to establish or
enforce our rights and interests or meet our regulatory obligations. We will
always balance our interests against your own to ensure it is fair.

The following processes rely on legitimate interest:
    • Call recording for quality and monitoring purposes and to confirm facts
    • Fraud and money laundering detection and prevention
    • Engaging and contacting our client throughout the lifecycle of their
      claim to ensure they have a good experience as a Wealthy PLR Limited
      client
    • Internally auditing our processes to maintain our high standards
    • Sharing data with external auditors where required under regulation,
      contracts or agreements
    • Sharing data with selected third parties in order to protect our rights
    • Sharing data with our regulators to meet our obligations
The transfer of data to Wealthy PLR Limited, if instructed by our client,
where we can no longer act for them due to a risk of or actual conflict of
interest.
Ensuring network information and security
Processing data relating to witnesses, litigation friends, persons acting under
a Power of Attorney or as Court Appointed Deputies, to assist our clients
with their claims.
If you have any further questions, don’t hesitate to contact us.
Our technology
We collect data about you through the use of technology such as cookies
and device fingerprinting. View our full Cookie Policy.
Your cookie preferences
Managing, Disabling And Enabling Cookies
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies from any website by
modifying the settings in your browser. If you wish to restrict or block the
cookies which are set by our website, you can do this through your browser
settings. For information about how to manage and disable cookies you can

use the ‘Help’ function within your browser or please visit
www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. However, please note
that by deleting or disabling cookies this could affect the functionality of our
website and you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our
site.
Confidentiality and disclosure of your data
We will endeavour to treat your personal data as private and confidential.
From time to time we may employ agents and subcontractors to process
your personal data on our behalf. The same duty of confidentiality and
security will apply to them and all processing will be carried out under our
instruction and with benefit of signed agreements.
We would like to bring to your attention our obligations to disclose data in
the following four exceptional cases permitted by law, and the other
situations set out below. These are:
    •  Where   we are legally compelled to do so
    •  Where   there is a duty to the public to disclose
    •  Where   disclosure is required to protect our interest
    •  Where   disclosure is made at your request or with your consent
If a complaint is made about the service we have provided, we may be
obliged to forward details about the complaint, including personal data, to
the relevant ombudsman. You can be assured that they are similarly obliged
to adhere to the requirements of the GDPR and keep personal data strictly
confidential.
Data subject rights
You have a number of rights as a data subject. Please note that these rights
do not apply in all circumstances.
Request your data
In order to access the data we hold about you, you need to make a ‘Subject
Access Request’, or SAR. To make a SAR please email us at:

Email contact:
support@plrexperts.com
Please provide:
Your name, email address, claim reference number and what information
you would like.
Identification documents; one which shows your name and signature (e.g. a
copy of your passport) and one which shows your name and address (e.g. a
copy of a recent bill or bank statement or other official document).
We will accept just one identification document if it shows your name,
address and signature such as a copy of your driving licence. (This is to take
reasonable steps to confirm your identity before providing you with details of
any personal information we may hold about you.)
Please note that if your SAR involves the personal data of other people, or
you are making a request on behalf of someone else (such as a parent on
behalf of their child), we may need identification from these individuals, as
well as a signed letter of authority from them confirming that they are happy
for you to act on their behalf and for us to release their data to you.
Once we have received your written request and identification documents,
we will have a month to fulfill your request. Where for some reason this will
not be possible, for instance due to large volumes of data being involved, we
are permitted by law to take up to an additional two months to fulfil your
request. Where any such delay is anticipated we will inform you of this,
along with the reason for the delay, within the first month of receiving your
request along with details of when we expect to be able to provide you with
the requested documentation.
Your other rights as a data subject, where applicable, include:
The right to be informed about our processing of your personal data
The right to have your personal data corrected if it is inaccurate, and to have
incomplete personal data completed
The right to object to the processing of your personal data

The right to have your personal data erased (“right to be forgotten”)
The right to move, copy, or transfer your personal data (“data portability”)
Rights regarding automated decision making, including profiling
For more details on these rights and how to exercise them, please contact:
support@plrexperts.com
If you have any queries about your rights, or believe that they have not
been met by Wealthy PLR Limited, please contact our Compliance Officer for
Legal Practice at:
support@plrexperts.com
If you have any complaints relating to the processing of your personal data,
you also have the right to complain to the relevant Supervisor Authority.
Retention of your data
Your personal data will be kept for as long as we require it in order to
provide our client with the agreed service. It will continue to be retained
after any service has been concluded or otherwise comes to an end in line
with our legal and regulatory requirements, and for as long as claims or
complaints may legally be brought against us.
Information Security
On our portal we protect any data you have given us by providing you with a
User ID and password. We also use industry standard security to encrypt
sensitive data in transit to our servers. As an extra precaution, CLEX
sessions will ‘time out’ if not used for 60 minutes.
It is not anticipated that we will need to transfer your personal data to other
companies or service providers located outside of the European Economic
Area. The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as
comprehensive as those in the UK or the EEA – but in the event that this is
necessary we will take steps to ensure that your data is given an equivalent
level of protection as it is in the EEA.

Show further information
Please be aware that communications over the Internet, such as emails, are
not secure unless they have been encrypted. Your communications may
route through a number of countries before being delivered – this is the
nature of the Internet. We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised
access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.
Additionally, you can protect your system by installing anti-virus and running
scans as recommended by the vendor. You should also run any security
updates / patches you receive for your system from the supplier.
Never respond to unsolicited emails from unfamiliar sources. Such emails
may be fraudulent and attempt to get you to provide your personal details or
payment information.
Changes to this policy
This privacy policy was last updated on 25th May 2018. We reserve the right
to make changes to this policy and you will be prompted of any changes
when you next visit our website.
From time to time we may need to change the way we use your personal
data. Where we believe you may not reasonably expect such a change we
will write to you. When we do so, you will have 60 days to object to the
change but if we do not hear from you within that time you consent to that
change.
